<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance on Alan Leung Github Project Page</title>
    <link>https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/tags/finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance on Alan Leung Github Project Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 5 - Stock Price Prediction in Python</title>
      <link>https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Description The program uses an artifical Recurrent Nerual Network (RNN) called Long Short Term Memory (LSTM) to predict the closing stock price of a corporation, like Apple Inc. using the past 60 day stock price.
Firstly, we import the library for computation processing. We get the stock quote from the website Yahoo using web.DataReader(), specifying the start date and end date of data extraction. Then we show the dataframe by commaning df, which comprises of 2270 rows (a day for a row), and 6 columns (Hig, Low, Open, Close, Volume, Adjusted Close).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3 - Sales Analysis Using Pandas</title>
      <link>https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alanspace.github.io/Alan_Portfolio_advanced/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Description This is a project using pandas to analyse the sales productivity. By means of data analysis, we can answer the following questions:
What was the best month for sales? How much was earned that month?   It makes sense that December is the best month of sales, becasue it is the period of Christmas and public holidays. People tend to buy presents for celebration.
What city sold the most product?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
